Guide to the Ellen McGowan Biddle Shipman papers, 1914-1946.
Shipman, Ellen McGowan Biddle papers, 1914-1946.
- Series IV. Project Files (Plans)
  - E.B. Schley (Map-case Folder 141-142)
    - Layout and grading plan of garden, 1926 (Map-case Folder 141)
    - Preliminary plan and specifications for walls, 1926 (Map-case Folder 141)
    - General construction plan of garden, 1926 (Map-case Folder 141)
    - Construction plan for pool A, 1926 (Map-case Folder 141)
    - Construction details of canvas roof for pergola, 1926 (Map-case Folder 141)
    - Garden sections, 1926 (Map-case Folder 142)
    - Details of grilles in upper garden, 1926 (Map-case Folder 142)
    - Shrub planting plan of upper garden, 1926 (Map-case Folder 142)
    - More garden sections, 1926 (Map-case Folder 142)
    - Details of wrought iron hand rail, 1926 (Map-case Folder 142)
    - Details of brick paving house terrace, 1926 (Map-case Folder 142)
    - Construction plan for pool B, 1926 (Map-case Folder 142)
    - General shrub planting plan for outside of wall, 1926 (Map-case Folder 142)
    - Flower planting plan for lower garden, 1926 (Map-case Folder 142)
    - Bulb planting plan for lower garden, 1926 (Map-case Folder 142)
    - Construction details for brick steps in upper garden, 1926 (Map-case Folder 142)
    - Details of wrought iron vine holder, 1926 (Map-case Folder 142)
    - Flower planting plan in upper garden, 1926 (Map-case Folder 142)
    - Bulb planting plan in upper garden, 1926 (Map-case Folder 142)
    - Details of awnings and standards (Blueprint), 1926 (Map-case Folder 142)
    - Details of wrought iron handrail (Blueprint), 1926 (Map-case Folder 142)
    - Details of posts along service walk, 1926 (Map-case Folder 142)
    - Construction details in garden (2 Blueprints), 1926 (Map-case Folder 142)
  - Mrs. Ellery Sedgwick (Map-case Folder 143)
    Location: Beverly, Massachusetts
    - Preliminary design plan (Photostat), 1930 (Map-case Folder 143)
  - Smithers (Map-case Folder 143)
    Location: Glen Cove, Long Island, New York
    - Detail of entrance portal and lattice arbor (Map-case Folder 143)
    - Sketch of pergola seat (Map-case Folder 143)
  - Alfred R. Shands (Map-case Folder 143)
    - Construction drawing for lath fence, 1937 (Map-case Folder 143)
  - Mr. and Mrs. William P. Stevens (Map-case Folder 143)
    - Sketch design plan, 1929 (Map-case Folder 143)
  - Glenn Stewart (Map-case Folder 143)
    Location: Locust Valley, Long Island, New York
    - Lattice design at pergola (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 143)
  - J.T. Stark (Map-case Folder 143)
    Location: Lauerock, Pennsylvania
    - Gate details (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 143)
  - Mr. William Watson Smith (Map-case Folder 144-145 and Mapcase Items 2-15)
    Location: Laughlintown (Pittsburgh), Pennsylvania
    - First floor plan of house (Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 144)
    - Detail of wood for brick piers (Map-case Folder 144)
    - Construction drawing gate and fence (Map-case Folder 144)
    - Suggested design plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 144)
    - Topographic plot plan (Map-case Folder 144)
    - Design sketch (Map-case Folder 144)
    - Details of entrance gate (Map-case Folder 144)
    - Tulip planting plan (Map-case Folder 144)
    - Plan for tulip in center borders (Map-case Folder 144)
    - Annual planting plan (Map-case Folder 145)
    - Detail of entrance fence (Map-case Folder 145)
    - Construction plan for garden balustrade (Map-case Folder 145)
    - Moulding detail (Map-case Folder 145)
    - Construction plan of garden seats (Map-case Folder 145)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 145)
    - Planting plan for area around pool (Map-case Folder 145)
    - Shrub planting plan for entrance drive (Map-case Folder 145)
    - Rose garden planting plan (Map-case Folder 145)
    - Revised garden layout plan (Map-case Folder 145)
    - House - First floor plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 145)
    - Construction plan for lily pool (Map-case Folder 145)
    - Construction plan for garden (Map-case Folder 145)
    - Bulb planting plan for garden, 1926 (Map-case Item 2)
    - Planting plan for east boundary to garden (matted) (Map-case Item 3)
    - Construction plan for wall (matted), 1924 (Map-case Item 4)
    - Bulb planting plan for garden, 1932 (Map-case Item 5)
    - Design plan for terraces (matted), 1930 (Map-case Item 6)
    - Construction detail of basin for wall fountain (matted), 1926 (Map-case Item 7)
    - Trees and shrubs planting plan for garden (matted), 1930 (Map-case Item 8)
    - Planting plan for perennials on terrace (matted), 1930 (Map-case Item 9)
    - Flower planting plan for garden (matted), 1926 (Map-case Item 10)
    - Shrub planting plan for garden, 1926 (Map-case Item 11)
    - Perennial planting plan for garden (matted), 1930 (Map-case Item 12)
    - General garden layout plan (matted), 1930 (Map-case Item 13)
    - Planting plan for entrance court (matted), undated (Map-case Item 14)
    - Furniture arrangement plan (matted) (Map-case Item 15)
  - Mr. and Mrs. George Secor (Map-case Folder 146)
    - Design plan, 1944 (Map-case Folder 146)
    - Preliminary studies for first floor plan (Black and White), 1944 (Map-case Folder 146)
    - Preliminary studies for second floor plan (Black and White), 1944 (Map-case Folder 146)
    - Sketches, 1944 (Map-case Folder 146)
    - Topographical survey (Photostat), 1944 (Map-case Folder 146)
    - Survey (Photostat), 1944 (Map-case Folder 146)
    - Design plan (2 copies), 1944 (Map-case Folder 146)
    - Revised design plan, 1944 (Map-case Folder 146)
    - Preliminary study for first floor plan, 1944 (Map-case Folder 146)
    - Plan for vegetable garden, 1944 (Map-case Folder 146)
    - Elevation studies (Black and White), 1944 (Map-case Folder 146)
    - Presentation drawings for proposed house (3 photostats), 1944 (Map-case Folder 146)
    - Preliminary studies - part plans of attic and basement, 1944 (Map-case Folder 146)
    - Preliminary studies - second floor plan, 1944 (Map-case Folder 146)
    - Study for house location (Blueprint), 1944 (Map-case Folder 146)
    - Suggestions for development, 1944 (Map-case Folder 146)
    - Topographic survey of property, 1944 (Map-case Folder 146)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Graham Stewart (Map-case Folder 147)
    Location: Graham, Texas
    - Construction details for wall and pool (Map-case Folder 147)
    - General tree and shrub planting plan (Map-case Folder 147)
    - Perennial and rose planting plan for west garden (Map-case Folder 147)
    - Perennial and rose planting plan for east garden (Map-case Folder 147)
    - General design plan (Map-case Folder 147)
    - Construction plan for gardens (Map-case Folder 147)
    - Sketch plan for gardens (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 147)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Hubert Smith (Map-case Folder 147)
    - Design plan for flower garden (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 147)
    - Revised design plan for flower gardens (Map-case Folder 147)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 147)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Ralph Smillie (Map-case Folder 147)
    - Plan for shady corner south of garden, 1943 (Map-case Folder 147)
    - Sketches, 1943 (Map-case Folder 147)
    - Preliminary sketch plan, 1943 (Map-case Folder 147)
    - Topographical map of property (Blueprint), 1943 (Map-case Folder 147)
    - Perennial planting plan for garden, 1943 (Map-case Folder 147)
    - Perennial planting plan for terrace, 1943 (Map-case Folder 147)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for terrace, 1943 (Map-case Folder 147)
    - Layout plan for terrace, 1943 (Map-case Folder 147)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for garden, 1943 (Map-case Folder 147)
    - Construction plan for pool (VOID), 1943 (Map-case Folder 147)
    - Construction details for pool, 1943 (Map-case Folder 147)
    - Construction details for walls and steps, 1943 (Map-case Folder 147)
    - Printed specifications, 1943 (Map-case Folder 147)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Henry B. Smith (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Construction plan for entrance road (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Design plan by Mrs. Henry Smith (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Planting plan for entrance (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Plan for development (Blueprint and Black and White) (Map-case Folder 148)
    - General construction plan (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Planting plan for grounds (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Design plan for garden (Map-case Folder 148)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Philip Strubling (Map-case Folder 148)
    - General plan (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Planting plan for entrance drive (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Plot plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 148)
  - Miss Eleanor Swayne (Map-case Folder 148)
    Location: Southampton, Long Island, New York
    - Shrub planting plan for area outside terraces (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for boundary (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Flowering shrub planting plan (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Elevation sketch of brick garden wall (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Shrub planting plan in annual garden (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Annual planting plan in cutting garden (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Revised sketch of picking garden (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Preliminary design for cutting garden (Map-case Folder 148)
    - General garden construction plan and details (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Construction plan for terraces (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Revised sketch A and B (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Sweat pea planting plan (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Foundation planting plan (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Dimensioned plan (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Map of part of property (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 148)
  - Miss Eleanor Swayne (Alfred Swayne) (Map-case Folder 148)
    Location: Southampton (Shinnecock Hills), Long Island, New York
    - Alterations to house - ground floor plan (Blueprint), 1928 (Map-case Folder 148)
      Goodwin, Thompson and Patterson, architects
    - Same as above with attached sketches for an individual room and fireplace, 1928 (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Kitchen porch (Blueprint), 1928 (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Sketch of plot plan for house, 1928 (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Blueprint of plot plan for house with lines added outside of dining room (Map-case Folder 148)
    - Ground plan (Blueprint), 1928 (Map-case Folder 148)
      William Miltenberger, architect
    - Cross-section of part of property of Ellen Swatyne, 1928 (Map-case Folder 148)
      by Wallace Halsey
  - F.M. Towle (Map-case Folder 149)
    - Trees and shrubs planting plan in green garden (Map-case Folder 149)
    - Construction drawing for gardens (Map-case Folder 149)
  - Mrs. James A. Thomas (Map-case Folder 149-150)
    - Construction detail for wall and niche (Map-case Folder 149)
    - Layout plan for garden wall (Map-case Folder 149)
    - Plan of property (Map-case Folder 149)
    - Plan showing changes in entrance drive and steps (Map-case Folder 149)
    - Construction details for garden fountain and pool (Map-case Folder 149)
    - Measured drawing for terrace and steps (Map-case Folder 149)
    - Construction details for walls (Map-case Folder 149)
    - Construction plan for new section of terrace (Map-case Folder 149)
    - Construction plan for brick steps at terrace (Map-case Folder 149)
    - Construction details for brick steps and walls (Map-case Folder 149)
    - Planting plan for perennial border (Map-case Folder 149)
    - Screen planting plan between drive and garden wall (Map-case Folder 149)
    - Bulb planting plan for garden (Map-case Folder 149)
    - Preliminary sketch plan (Map-case Folder 149)
    - Revised sketch for tool house and greenhouse (Map-case Folder 149)
    - Planting plan for flower garden (Map-case Folder 149)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for section A and B (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 149)
    - Sketch for gates 1-3 (Map-case Folder 149)
    - Planting plan for cutting garden (Map-case Folder 149)
    - Topographic plan of property (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 149)
    - Wrought iron details (Map-case Folder 150)
    - Planting plan for trees and shrubs (Map-case Folder 150)
    - Planting plan for perennial border (Map-case Folder 150)
    - Sketch of alteration and addition to house (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 150)
    - Planting at rock wall (Map-case Folder 150)
    - Sketch for tool house and greenhouse (Map-case Folder 150)
  - Mrs. George Talbot (Map-case Folder 150)
    - Planting plan for perennial border, 1937 (Map-case Folder 150)
    - Sketches, 1937 (Map-case Folder 150)
  - Mrs. Eugene Taliaferro (Map-case Folder 150)
    Location: Oyster Bay, Long Island, New York
    - Design plan for garden (Map-case Folder 150)
    - Construction plan and details for walls and steps (Map-case Folder 150)
    - Plan of existing grades (Photostat) (Map-case Folder 150)
    - Survey of property (Photostat) (Map-case Folder 150)
    - Preliminary design plan for gardens (Map-case Folder 150)
    - Planting plan for gardens (Map-case Folder 150)
    - Alternations to residence (2 Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 150)
  - M.D. Truesdale (Map-case Folder 151-152)
    - General planting plan (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Construction plan of pool terrace (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Tulip planting plan of east garden (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Revised planting plan of upper terrace (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Wrought iron details for gate (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Detail of garden walls (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for road (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Measured drawing for gate in lower garden (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Planting plan for entrance driveway (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Ground cover planting plan for pool terrace (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Preliminary sketch plan (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Measured drawing for entrance gate (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Sketch design plan (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Sketch plan for evergreen garden (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Construction plan for evergreen garden (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Revised detail for terrace wall (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Construction plan for pool terrace (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Plan for terrace and entrance steps (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Planting plan of forecourt (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Shrub and bulb planting plan for east garden (Map-case Folder 151)
    - General grading plan (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Construction plan for changes in west garden (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Revised planting plan for west garden (Map-case Folder 151)
    - Suggested change in west garden (Map-case Folder 152)
    - Spring bulb planting plan for east garden, upper level (Map-case Folder 152)
    - Biennial planting plan for east garden, upper level (Map-case Folder 152)
    - Chrysanthemum planting plan for east garden, upper level (Map-case Folder 152)
    - Details of walls around forecourt (Map-case Folder 152)
    - Bulb planting plan for evergreen garden (Map-case Folder 152)
    - Revised planting plan for garden (Map-case Folder 152)
    - Revised planting plan for new garden (Map-case Folder 152)
    - Construction plan for evergreen garden (Map-case Folder 152)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for road (Map-case Folder 152)
    - Measured drawing layout of garden walls (Map-case Folder 152)
    - General construction plan (Map-case Folder 152)
    - Details of forecourt walls (VOID) (Map-case Folder 152)
    - Perennial planting plan for evergreen garden (Map-case Folder 152)
    - Construction and planting plan for vegetable garden (Map-case Folder 152)
    - Construction plan for east garden walls (Map-case Folder 152)
    - Details for stone forecourt wall (Map-case Folder 152)
    - Construction details of door in northeast wall (Map-case Folder 152)
    - Details for driveway entrance (Map-case Folder 152)
    - Sketch design plan (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 152)
    - Plans of residence (Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 152)
    - Construction drawing for garden (Map-case Folder 152)
    - Preliminary sketch plan (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 152)
    - Flower planting plan for east garden (Map-case Folder 152)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Carl L. Tucker (Map-case Folder 153-157, 195a-g, 197)
    - Sketch for rose trellis, 1947 (Map-case Folder 153)
    - Steps for entrance (Blueprint), 1947 (Map-case Folder 153)
    - Revised construction plan for south wall and gateway, top terrace (Blueprint), 1947 (Map-case Folder 153)
    - Details of fountain piping (Blueprint), 1947 (Map-case Folder 153)
    - Fountain and hydrant piping system (Blueprint), 1947 (Map-case Folder 153)
    - Detail of steps from enclosed garden (Blueprint), 1947 (Map-case Folder 153)
    - Pit house drawing, 1947 (Map-case Folder 153)
    - Details of pergola (Blueprint), 1947 (Map-case Folder 153)
    - Tulip planting plan in parterre garden (Blueprint), 1947 (Map-case Folder 153)
    - Bulb planting plan in enclosed garden, 1947 (Map-case Folder 153)
    - Perennial planting plan in enclosed garden (Blueprint), 1947 (Map-case Folder 153)
    - Revised shrub planting plan in enclosed garden, 1947 (Map-case Folder 153)
    - Details of pergola beams and pole, 1947 (Map-case Folder 153)
    - Details of pergola, 1947 (Map-case Folder 153)
    - Design for tennis shelter and colonnade (Black and White), 1947 (Map-case Folder 153)
    - Herb planting plan in parterre garden, 1947 (Map-case Folder 153)
    - Annual planting plan in enclosed garden, 1947 (Map-case Folder 153)
    - Shrub planting plan in main garden, 1947 (Map-case Folder 154)
    - Construction plan of paths, 1947 (Map-case Folder 154)
    - Flower planting plan for main garden - Sheet A and B, 1947 (Map-case Folder 154)
    - Design plan for gardens, 1947 (Map-case Folder 154)
    - Sketches, 1947 (Map-case Folder 154)
    - Plan of perennial border, 1947 (Map-case Folder 154)
    - Planting plan for addition to guest house, 1947 (Map-case Folder 154)
    - First floor plan for guest house (Blueprint), 1947 (Map-case Folder 154)
    - Planting plan for new rose beds, 1947 (Map-case Folder 154)
    - Revised planting plan for new rose beds, 1947 (Map-case Folder 154)
    - Shrub location plan, 1947 (Map-case Folder 154)
    - Tulip planting plan in parterre garden, 1947 (Map-case Folder 154)
    - Design plan for superintendent’s garden, 1947 (Map-case Folder 154)
    - Dimension drawing doe rose beds, 1947 (Map-case Folder 154)
    - Revised design plan for superintendent's garden, 1947 (Map-case Folder 154)
    - Flower planting plan for upper terraces, 1947 (Map-case Folder 154)
    - Revised planting for beds E and F in picking garden (Blueprint), 1947 (Map-case Folder 154)
    - Revised planting for beds C and D in picking garden (Blueprint), 1947 (Map-case Folder 155)
    - Sketch plan for herb garden, 1947 (Map-case Folder 154)
    - Suggested arrangement of iron grilles in east wall, 1947 (Map-case Folder 154)
    - Plan for ground covers under bulbs in parterre garden, 1947 (Map-case Folder 155)
    - Bulb planting plan for enclosed garden, 1947 (Map-case Folder 155)
    - Perennial planting plan for parterre garden, 1947 (Map-case Folder 155)
    - Revised central fountain details - Scheme A (Blueprint), 1947 (Map-case Folder 155)
    - Suggestions for wrought iron gate (Blueprint), 1947 (Map-case Folder 155)
    - Revised central fountain details - Scheme B, 1947 (Map-case Folder 155)
    - Construction detail for wall fountain, 1947 (Map-case Folder 155)
    - Revised planting plan for beds A and B in picking garden, 1947 (Map-case Folder 155)
    - Sketch plan for gardens, 1947 (Map-case Folder 155)
    - Notes and details of pool construction, 1947 (Map-case Folder 155)
    - Details of enclosed garden steps, 1947 (Map-case Folder 155)
    - Planting plan for picking garden, 1947 (Map-case Folder 155)
    - Shrub planting plan for area around garage, 1947 (Map-case Folder 155)
    - Central fountain details, 1947 (Map-case Folder 155)
    - Construction details for wooden door in upper terrace wall, 1947 (Map-case Folder 155)
    - Revised central fountain details, 1947 (Map-case Folder 155)
    - Revised construction plan for south wall of upper terrace, 1947 (Map-case Folder 155)
    - Construction plan of terrace, 1947 (Map-case Folder 155)
    - Iris planting plan for main garden, 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - Grading plan for gardens, 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - Steps for service entrance, 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - Construction details of seat (Blueprint), 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - Details of central fountain, 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - Plan and elevation of garden entrance, 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - Shrub and tree planting plan for grounds, 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - Shrub and planting plan along driveway, 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - Tennis court shelter plans and elevations (Blueprints), 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - Grading plan of gardens, 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - General design plan of gardens, 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - Grading plan of garden terraces, 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - Topographical map of western portion of grounds, 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - Grading and wall plans for gardens, 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - Construction plan for third terrace, 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - Hydrant location plan of gardens, 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - Construction plan of south wall of top terrace, 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - Details of pergola, 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - Sketch of wrought iron gate (Blueprint), 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - West elevation of residence (Blueprint), 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - Suggestion for wrought iron door hardware (Blueprint), 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - Location of iron grille in west wall, 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - Plan of foundations for wall fountains, 1947 (Map-case Folder 156)
    - Grading plan around house, 1947 (Map-case Folder 157)
    - Stone details, 1947 (Map-case Folder 157)
    - Fountain and hydrant piping system (Blueprint), 1947 (Map-case Folder 157)
    - Details of steps in the flower garden, 1947 (Map-case Folder 157)
    - Planting plan for cutting garden (VOID), 1947 (Map-case Folder 157)
    - Pergola details, 1947 (Map-case Folder 157)
    - Water piping and drainage plan, 1947 (Map-case Folder 157)
    - Entrance arch details, 1947 (Map-case Folder 157)
    - Plan showing suggested garden grading, 1947 (Map-case Folder 157)
    - Details of wrought iron fences at pergola, 1947 (Map-case Folder 157)
    - Revised central fountain details, 1947 (Map-case Folder 157)
    - Suggested wrought iron gate (Blueprint), 1947 (Map-case Folder 157)
    - Pergola details, 1947 (Map-case Folder 157)
    - Central portion of flower garden south of house, 1922 (Map-case Folder 195a)
    - Rustic shelter in the flower garden, 1922 (Map-case Folder 195a)
    - Planting plan for bird sanctuary (Blueprint), undated (Map-case Folder 195b)
    - Planting plan for bulbs in the parterre garden, 1939, 1941, 1947 (Map-case Folder 195c)
    - Bulb plan for main garden and terraces (Blueprint), 1924 (Map-case Folder 195d)
    - Flower planting plan for main garden (Blueprint), undated (Map-case Folder 195e)
    - Shrub planting plan for upper terraces, 1924 (Map-case Folder 195f)
    - Shrub planting plan for main garden, 1924 (Map-case Folder 195g)
    - General design plan for gardens, 1924 (Map-case Folder 197)
  - Mrs. J.A. Vietnor (Map-case Folder 158)
    - Bamboo trellis details (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 158)
  - Mrs. Baroness Maud Ledyard von Kettcher (Map-case Folder 158)
    Location: Canaan (Falls Village), Connecticut
    - Topographic plan of a portion of property ( (Map-case Folder 158)
    - Design plan, 1945 (Map-case Folder 158)
    - Revised design plan, 1945 (Map-case Folder 158)